我们要出门了  再见
Okay, we're headed out-- See you later.
你俩走之前
Before you leave,
能帮我测试一下这降噪耳机吗
could you test these noise-cancelling headphones?
好呀
Yeah, sure. Okay.
开始吧
Go ahead.
你好  能听见我说话吗
Hello, can you hear me?
谢尔顿  咱家水壶里的
Sheldon, I haven't changed the filter
滤水器已经两年没换过了
in the water pitcher in two years.
伯纳黛特给你取了个外号叫处子鸡尾酒
Uh, Bernadette's nickname for you is the virgin pina colada.
你收藏的乔治·卢卡斯签名其实是我的签名
Your George Lucas autograph is really a "me" autograph.
有一次我懒得走回我家去
Yeah, well, once I was too lazy to walk across the hall,
于是我借用了你的牙刷
so I used your toothbrush.
还有一次你睡着了
Ooh, and one time when you were asleep,
艾米脱掉了她的...
Amy totally took off her...
...所以你才是百里挑一的好室友
And that's why you're the best roommate ever.
真可惜我没听到这些好话
Now I'm sad I didn't hear it.
你拿这降噪耳机干嘛用呢
So what do you need the headphones for?
我这几个月一直在研究
Well, I've been struggling for months
暗物质中质子
to come up with a theory of dark matter
不衰变的问题
that doesn't make protons decay.
我希望能靠优化工作环境的办法
I'm hoping to finally tackle it
来解决这个问题
by optimizing my work environment.
所以我准备了最佳饮用温度的茶
See, I've got, uh, my tea is at the perfect sipping temperature.
穿上了加绒的四角内裤
Uh, I have fleece-lined boxer shorts
保暖我的小屁屁
to keep my tushie toasty.
最后但也是同样重要的一点
And then, oh, last but not least,
这张激励人心的猫咪海报
this inspirational cat poster,
上面印着物理学界的叛徒
improved with the reassuring face
理查德·费曼和蔼可亲的脸
of physics renegade Richard Feynman.
这就是你昨晚带他去文具店的原因吗
Is that why you had to take him to Office Depot last night?
我不想聊这件事
I don't want to talk about it.
好了  这地盘归你了
There, the place is all yours.
好好玩吧
Yeah, have fun.
我会的  没有比改变世界的
Oh, I will-- nothing more fun
科学之夜更让人开心的了
than a paradigm-shifting evening of science.
你却说替我搓澡才是最开心的事
And you thought it was soaping me up in the shower.
拜拜
Bye.
好了
Okay.
开始吧
Here we go.
质子衰变
Proton decay.
我们回来了
Hey, we're home.
有什么进展吗
Any progress?
怎么可能有进展
How could there be?!
你们老是打扰我
With these constant interruptions.
我爱他  但如果他坏掉了  我们别再买新的了
I love him, but if he's broken, let's not get a new one.
你在干什么  该上班了
What are you doing? It's time to go.
我今天不去上班
I'm not going to work today.
你想知道为什么吗
And would you like to know why?
你不高兴  因为你花了一整晚
Ah, you're upset because you spent the whole night working
研究暗物质却找不到突破口
on dark matter and didn't make a breakthrough,
现在你担心转换研究方向的决定是错误的
and now you're worried you made a huge mistake switching fields,
于是你要窝在家里生一整天闷气
and you're gonna sit around and sulk all day?
就像一个大宝宝
Like a big old baby.
有需要给我打电话
Call me if you need anything.
我在这里闷太久了
I've been cooped up in here too long.
也许我需要点新鲜空气
Maybe I need some fresh air.
佩妮
Penny?
什么事
Ugh, what?
听起来你很痛苦
You sounded in distress.
我担心你是不是遇到了麻烦
I was worried something unpleasant was happening to you.
比如有人要谋杀你
Like a murder.
或者是莱纳德突然找你滚床单
Or spontaneous coitus with Leonard.
我只是在锻炼  讨厌死了
Oh, I'm just doing this awful workout. I hate it.
如果你讨厌  干嘛还要做呢
Well, if you hate it, then why are you doing it?
当然我对你和莱纳德滚床单这件事
Although I could ask the same question
也有同样的问题
about coitus with Leonard.
我想  我就是喜欢这种讨厌它的感觉吧
I don't know-- I guess I like that I hate it.
可以激发我的斗志
It makes me work harder.
-你是指...  -我是指锻炼  谢尔顿
- And to clarify... - The exercise, Sheldon.
你不是应该准备上班了吗
Shouldn't you be getting ready for work?
我今天不上班
I'm not going.
你想知道为什么吗
Would you like to know why?
你不高兴  因为你昨晚什么都没搞出来
Uh, you're sad about not getting anything done last night,
所以你要窝在家里生一整天闷气
so you're gonna sit around and pout about it?
我完全不如自己预期的那么神秘莫测啊
Boy, I'm not nearly as mysterious as I think I am.
-我发明了一个游戏  想玩吗  -好啊
- I invented a game. You want to play? - Sure.
名字叫"艾米丽还是小桂子"
It's called "Emily or Cinnamon""
我告诉你们拉杰曾经说过的话
I give you actual quotes I've heard Raj say,
你来猜一猜这些话的对象是女朋友  还是狗
and you guess if he was talking to his girlfriend or his dog.
好啊  你想笑就笑吧
Go ahead, make fun.
我可不会觉得尴尬
You can't embarrass me.
我有一个漂亮女友
I've got a beautiful girlfriend
和一条爱我爱到愿意喝我洗澡水的狗
and a dog who loves me so much she drinks my bathwater.
很好  这是对谁说的  艾米丽还是小桂子
Okay, who was he talking to, Emily or Cinnamon:
"你要知道  你不在的时候
"I want you to know, the bed feels so lonely
空荡荡的床显得好孤单"
when you're not in it."
我可不怎么喜欢这个游戏
I may not be liking this game so much.
小桂子  再来一个
Cinnamon. Give me another one.
好的  艾米丽还是小桂子
Okay, Emily or Cinnamon:
"看看  我给咱俩买了情侣毛衣"
"Check it out, I got us matching sweaters!"
我们都收到了他的圣诞卡  当然是小桂子
We all got the Christmas card-- Cinnamon.
一个男人可以同时关爱他的女人和他的狗
You know, a man can care deeply about a woman and a pet.
这并不奇怪
It's not strange.
艾米丽  这话我听过他对艾米丽说过
Ooh, Emily. I heard him say that to Emily.
你不是要待在家里吗
Hey, I thought you were staying home.
是的  但和佩妮聊过之后
Yeah, I was, but after talking to Penny,
我发现了一件事
I realized something.
我...首先  她为了保持对你的吸引力
I... first, she's trying much harder to stay attractive
付出的努力可比你多
in this relationship than you are.
其次
And second...
我毫无进展的原因就是
the reason I may not be progressing in my research is
我为自己打造的环境太舒适了
I've created too pleasant of an environment for myself.
什么意思
What do you mean?
根据叶杜二氏的心理学实验
According to a classic psychological experiment
想提高工作效率
by Yerkes and Dodson, in order to maximize performance,
就必须营造一种焦虑紧张的气氛
one must create a state of productive anxiety.
所以我希望你们能帮我个忙
So I'd like to ask you all to do something for me.
别让我放松下来
Keep me on my toes.
攻我不备
Just throw me off my game.
最重要的是  使劲浑身解数让我难受
E-Essentially, go out of your way to make my life miserable.
等等
Hold on.
这么做对我们有什么好处
What's in it for us?
-我觉得吧..  -好  我们同意了
- Well, I suppose... - Okay, we'll do it!
做完了
Done.
33秒
33 seconds.
这就是我们的基准线
Okay, that'll be our baseline.
我不想教你怎么工作
You know, I don't want to tell you how to do your job,
不过如果一只老鼠走通了迷宫
but when a mouse completes a maze,
它会得到饲料奖励
it gets a food pellet.
它的大脑还会被镊子夹出来呢
It also gets its brain plucked out with tweezers.
而它的最后一餐只是一颗饲料
And his last meal was a food pellet?
你真是禽兽
You're a monster.
好了  接下来  我们要逐步
All right, next, we're gonna introduce
加强紧张焦虑刺激  测量你的应力水平
an anxiety-inducing stimulus, measure your stress levels
观察它对你思考能力的影响
and see how it affects your problem-solving rate.
很好
Very well.
祝你好运  人家可是个淡定哥哦
And good luck-- I'm a pretty laid-back guy.
准备好了吗
Ready?
开始
Begin.
你为什么要戳破
Why'd you pop it?
对不起  我本来瞄准的是你的心脏
I'm sorry, I was aiming for your heart.
我知道你不喜欢
Look, I know you don't like it,
但这是实验的意义所在
but that's the point of the experiment.
我需要激怒你
I need to irritate you
来找到你的最佳焦虑区
to find your optimal anxiety zone.
而且你不要挠痒痒  波尔卡舞曲或看我吃香蕉
And you said no to tickling, polka music or watching me eat a banana.
谁会横着啃香蕉啊
Who eats them horizontally?!
我妈说好女孩都是这么吃的
My mother said that's how good girls do it.
也许这是浪费时间
Perhaps this was a waste of time.
谢尔顿
Sheldon,
你是了不起的科学家
you're a remarkable scientist.
耐心一点  我确信你会找到一直寻觅的
Just be patient-- I'm sure you'll find the breakthrough
突破口
you've been looking for.
谢谢
Thank you.
而且如果你只进行可靠研究
And if you only do solid research
而不是有开创性的发现
instead of making a groundbreaking discovery,
那又有什么关系呢
what does it matter?
只进行可靠研究
"Only do solid research"?!
我来找你帮忙  你却侮辱我
Uh... I come to you for help, and you insult me?!
我原以为你至少可以...
I thought the least that you would do would be...
看  你的焦虑水平达标了
Look, your anxiety levels are right in the zone.
真的吗
Really?
真是太好了
Oh, that's fantastic.
慢着  又落下去了
N-Now, wait, they're dropping.
为什么落下去了
Why are they dropping?
因为你开心数值提高了
Because you're happy they're elevated.
真是气死我了
Oh, that is infuriating!
看  又上升了
Ooh, look, they went back up again.
太好了
Terrific.
不好  又落下去了
Oh, no, they went back down!
各位  你们想玩什么游戏
All right, guys, what game do you want to play?
来看看
Let's see.
不如玩"艾米丽或小桂子"
How about "Emily or Cinnamon""
知道吗  你记得我说过的这些话
You know what? I think it's a little weird
感觉有点奇怪
that you remember me saying all these things.
也许真相是  你嫉妒我所拥有的这些关系
Maybe the truth is-- you're jealous of all my relationships.
也许我是嫉妒
Oh, maybe I am.
谁不想做这样的女孩
Who wouldn't want to be the girl,
也有可能是狗  听到以下的话
or possibly dog, to hear the words:
"你真幸运
"You're so lucky.
你有着最闪亮的头发[毛发]"
You have the shiniest hair""
好难抉择
That is a tough one.
我知道他既帮女友梳发  也帮狗梳毛
Uh, I-I know he brushes both of them.
-先生们  -在
- Gentlemen... - Yeah.
我想到了你们激怒我的最完美方法
I have figured out the perfect way for you to irritate me.
我想你们做我的智力拳击陪练
I'd like you to be my intellectual sparring partners.
从现在开始  我发表的任何言论
From now on, when I make an assertion,
你们都要提出质疑
I need you to challenge it.
就是说  你说什么我们都反对吗
So you just want us to disagree with whatever you say?
是的
Yes.
-你觉得这样有帮助  -是的
- And you think that's going to help? - Yes.
我觉得这样做完全没帮助
Well, I don't think that's gonna help at all.
不  会有的
Oh, no, it will.
我的大脑保持忙碌  我会更专心
See, by keeping my mind engaged, I'll become more focused.
霍华德说得对  这招不会有用的
Howard's right-- that'll never work.
别就管不管用反对我  这完全是有科学依据的
Stop fighting me on the premise. It's scientifically valid.
我会提出命题
I'm going to advance propositions,
我只是需要你们质疑我
I just want you to challenge me.
我觉得这完全不是你想要的
I don't think that's what you want at all.
这当然是我想要的
Why, of course it's what I want.
如果不是  我为什么会说这是我想要的
Why would I say it's what I want if it's not what I want?
因为这是你想要的  却不是你所说的
Because it is what you want, and it's not what you said.
我要求你们做这么简单的事  你们都做不到
I ask you for one simple thing, and you can't even do it.
我们可以
Yes, we can.
-那就照做  -就不
- Yeah, well, then do it. - Nah.
你们差劲死了
You guys are the worst.
谢谢  我想刚才有帮助
Thank you, I think that was helpful.
季度内最佳销售人员
Whichever rep has the best sales for the quarter
可以赢得二人夏威夷之行
gets a trip for two to Hawaii.
你和莱纳德去真是太浪漫了
That would be so romantic for you and Leonard.
显然你没见过他在沙滩上
Yeah, clearly you haven't seen him on the beach
拿着金属宝藏探测器乱走的样子
walking around with his metal detector.
如果我去夏威夷
If I were going to Hawaii,
我就整天待在凯克天文台
I'd spend all my time at the Keck Observatory.
你们知道吗  那里的望远镜
Did you know that the telescopes there
比哈勃望远镜的分辨率还高
have better resolution than the Hubble?
是吗
Really?
你想去夏威夷吗
Want to go to Hawaii?
女士们
Ladies?
Ladies...
女士们
Ladies?
进来
Come in.
女士们
Ladies.
什么事
What's up?
你们也许知道  我在做提高
As you may know, I've been experimenting
焦虑水平的实验
with elevated anxiety levels,
我想
and I thought,
最能提升我的不安的方法
what better way to increase my discomfort
就是让自己投身一晚
than to subject myself to an evening
枯燥乏味百无禁忌的性器官话题
of tasteless uncensored crotch talk?
你觉得我们平常的话题都是什么
What exactly do you think goes on here?
就是些
Well...
如果有异性在场时
conversations that you wouldn't be comfortable having
会令你们说起来尴尬的话题
in front of the opposite sex.
比如  谁的子宫颈最好
You know, who has the best cervix.
现在最流行哪种卫生棉
Which sanitary napkin is all the rage right now.
男士的臀部  以及你们渴望拍打和揉捏它
Men's buttocks, and how you want to pat and squeeze them.
我们在聊佩妮的工作
We were talking about Penny's job.
她傲慢兼暴脾气
And how difficult it is to do
又来大姨妈时  多难相处吗
when she's bloated, cranky and crampy?
继续吧
Continue.
谢尔顿  我们只是普通人
Sheldon, we are just people.
我们聊的和你们男生聊的一样
We talk about the same things you guys talk about.
你们在聊狼人是否能游泳吗
You talk about if werewolves can swim?
莱纳德说可以
See, Leonard says yes,
但我说得看那人在被咬变身前
but I say it depends on if the human could swim
会不会游泳  你们说呢
before he was bitten. What do you think?
咱们来聊月经吧
Let's just talk about our periods.
慢着
No, hold on.
所有犬类天生就会游泳
All canines instinctively know how to swim.
为什么狼人不能拥有这种能力呢
Why wouldn't a werewolf have the same abilities?
他们不是百分百狼
Well, they're not a hundred percent wolf.
他们是狼人  只有部分是狼
They're a werewolf-- that's only part wolf.
就好比拿苹果和橙子作比较
It's like comparing apples to oranges.
谢谢
Thank you.
确切来说  是满月时  苹果变成了
Oh, and technically, it's apples that turn into were-oranges
狼橙子
when the moon is full.
真好玩
Hey, this is fun.
改天你们都没有经前综合症时我们再聊
We should do it sometime when you aren't all PMS'ing.
再见
Bye.
出什么事了
What is going on?
我要令焦虑保持在正确的水平
Uh, I need to keep my anxiety at the right level,
所以我用黑武士  《蝙蝠侠》小丑以及哥斯拉的咆哮
so I'm using Darth Vader, the Joker, and Godzilla's roar
来令我保持在这一最佳状态
to keep me in that sweet spot.
我试着在里面加入泰勒·斯威夫特的歌
Uh, I tried including Taylor Swift in the mix,
结果发现我爱死她了
but turns out I love her.
至少戴耳机听吧
Well, at least listen to it through headphones.
我还想睡觉呢  晚安
I'm trying to sleep. Good night.
瞧这脾气
Boy!
泰勒没错  憎恨者就会黑  黑  黑你[歌词]
Taylor was right-- haters gonna hate, hate, hate, hate, hate.
最近你一直在工作
You've been working so much lately,
我很高兴你没有忘记约会之夜
I'm glad you didn't forget about date night.
当然了
Of course.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
在
Yeah.
或许你想收起笔记本  跟我聊聊天
Maybe you want to put the notebook away and talk to me.
我可以双管齐下
I can do both.
我的大脑现在处于最佳工作状态
No, my brain is working at optimal capacity.
我可以一边与你进行交谈
No, I can have a conversation with you
同时一边解决暗物质质子衰变问题
and solve the dark matter proton decay problem at the same time.
好吧  你今天好吗
Fine. How was your day?
对  你说得对
Oh, you said it.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
谢尔顿  我很担心你
Sheldon, I'm worried about you.
你不吃饭
You're not eating,
也几天都没睡觉了
you haven't slept in days,
而且说实话  那帽子已经开始发臭了
and, to be honest, that cap is starting to smell.
我知道
I know.
这酸爽取代了哥斯拉叫声
It's replaced Godzilla
成为了焦虑的主要来源
as my principle source of anxiety.
好  现在一票投艾米丽  一票投小桂子
Okay, so it's one vote Emily, one vote Cinnamon.
佩妮  你这一票至关重要
Penny, you're the tiebreaker.
再念一遍原句
Say the quote again.
"太完美了  我们都是天秤座"
"It's just so perfect that we're both Libras."
太难选了
Wow, this is hard.
我要选小桂子
I'm gonna say Cinnamon.
-正确  -太棒了
- Yes! - Yes!
不是吧
Come on!
那是最后一题了  我保证
That was the last one, I promise.
以后不会玩了
We won't play anymore.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果被她发现了  会伤害她感情的
'Cause if she ever found out, it would hurt her feelings.
艾米丽的感情吗
Emily's feelings?
对  艾米丽
Yes, Emily.
-准  -干的漂亮
- Nice! Yay! - Good job!
随便啦  谢尔顿呢
Whatever. Where's Sheldon?
约会之夜
Date night.
艾米可要遭罪了
Mmm, that can't be much fun for Amy.
今天上班的时候  他喝了有生以来第一罐红牛
You know, at work today, he tried his first Red Bull.
然后怎么了
What happened?
他在院子里追了一阵子松鼠  然后...
He chased a squirrel around the quad for a while and...
在我车里吐了
...then threw up in my car.
你们不觉得应该拦着他别做了吗
Don't you think you should make him stop all this?
我不确定  他也没伤害到别人
I don't know-- he's not really hurting anybody.
那是因为储物箱的呕吐物不是你清
You didn't have to scoop vomit out of your glove compartment.
他完成了很多工作
He is getting a lot of work done.
在质子衰变方面有了不错的发现
He had a pretty interesting take on proton decay.
如果他能破解  那会改变世界的  同志们
Wow, if he cracks that, it's a game changer, guys.
那将会彻底重新定义
It'll completely redefine our understanding
我们对物质宇宙的理解
of the physical universe.
没有错
Hmm, it would.
好啦  欢迎回到"艾米丽还是小桂子"
Okay, back to "Emily or Cinnamon""
"如此娇小的身躯  怎吃得下硕大的牛排"
"How can such a little girl eat such a big steak""
谢尔顿
Sheldon,
我要你把那帽子摘了
I want you to take that cap off.
你这唠叨的语气有助于增长焦虑
That nagging tone is helping my anxiety, yeah.
如果你的高音调能降低百分之十的话
But if you could maybe just go ten percent less shrill,
那你真是我的小呀小苹果了
that'd really put the zip-a-dee in my doo-dah.
抱歉  但你知道
I'm sorry, but you know we agreed
约会夜是不应该工作的
not to bring work to date night.
这就对了  完美
There you go, perfect.
谢尔顿  住手  我不是在开玩笑
Sheldon, stop it, I'm not kidding.
把帽子脱了  笔记本拿开
Take the cap off, and put the notebook away.
可我辛苦了几个月  终于开始有点突破
But after months of struggling, I'm finally making progress.
你没有必要为了工作  逼疯自己啊
You don't need to drive yourself crazy in order to be productive.
没必要吗
Or do I, hmm?
艾萨克·牛顿爵士在相信自己是犰狳时
Sir Isaac Newton wrote his Principia
才写出了《自然哲学的数学原理》
while convinced he was an armadillo.
没这回事
That's not true.
好吧  也许是  也许不是
Yeah, well, maybe it is, maybe it isn't.
我最近开始有幻觉了
I have been hallucinating lately.
谢尔顿  你必须停下来了
Sheldon, this has to stop.
你得去睡觉  照顾好自己的身体
You need to get some sleep and take care of yourself.
艾米  我这几天的收获
Amy, I have gotten more done in the last few days
比我开始研究暗物质以来全部加起来都多
than I have since I made the switch to dark matter.
万一我不继续下去  思路都不见了呢
What if I stop doing this, and it all goes away?
你的思路和想法来自于你  而非你的焦虑
Your thoughts and ideas come from you, not from your anxiety.
也许吧
Hmm, perhaps.
但我不会摘掉帽子的
But I'm not taking the cap off.
你折磨你自己是一回事
It's one thing to make yourself miserable,
但你让周围的人也都很痛苦
but you're making everyone around you miserable, too.
我最后再跟你说一遍  把帽子摘掉
Now, I'm telling you for the last time-- take the cap off.
是吗
Really?
我要是不摘呢
What if I don't?
在你回答问题之前  能把我的甜点上了吗
And before you answer that, can I have my dessert?
然后她就把我赶出去了
And then she threw me out.
我  可是她的亲男朋友啊
Me, her very own boyfriend.
我所做的一切都是在帮助人类
When all I've done is try to help humanity reach
对我们生活的世界有更深刻的理解
a more profound understanding of the world we live in.
这就是女人嘛
Yeah, well, women--
你拿她们有什么办法
what are you gonna do?
我就知道你能理解  艾萨克·牛顿犰狳
I knew you'd understand, Armadillo Isaac Newton.
好了
Okay...
我们到了
Here we are.
你们有什么诡计
What are you trying to pull?
科学部长又不在这
The president of science isn't in here.
你躺好了他马上就来
You lie down, he'll be here in a minute.
好的
Okay.
我还以为你们要骗我呢
Hey, I thought you were trying to trick me.
现在你舒舒服服地躺好了
Now, you just get comfortable.
不行  安逸是敌人
No, no, comfort is the enemy.
你知道什么叫舒服吗
You know what's comfortable?
拖鞋  毛毯和大熊猫
Slippers and blankets and panda bears.
想象一只长着理查德·费曼脸的熊猫
Imagine a panda bear with Richard Feynman's face on it.
暖暖车  莱纳德  海报时间到
Warm up the car, Leonard, it's poster time.
早上再说
Maybe in the morning.
对  你先睡一会
Yeah, you get some sleep.
不  我不想睡觉  你们强迫不了我
No, I don't want to go to sleep-- you can't make me.
你说的对  我们不能
You're right, we can't.
你们当然办不到
Yeah, darn straight, you can't.
竟然想哄一位成年人去睡觉...
Try to tell a grown man to go to sleep...
* 软软的小猫 *
* Soft kitty *
* 暖暖的小猫 *
* Warm kitty *
* 一只小毛球 *
* Little ball of fur... *
没用的
That's not gonna work.
* 快乐的小猫  瞌睡的小猫*
* Happy kitty, sleepy kitty *
* 喵 *
* Purr *
* 喵  喵 *
* Purr, purr *
他有时的确是个烦人精
You know, he can be a lot of trouble,
但看到他躺在那边就这样睡着
but when I see him lying here asleep like this,
我就想...
I just think...
把枕头按他脸上多简单啊
how easy it would be to hold a pillow over his face.
看来你休息得不错
Wow, you look like you got some rest.
我感觉好多了
Oh, I'm feeling much better.
而且我不用故意提升我的焦虑程度
And I've also been continuing to make progress
工作也顺利进展中
without artificially raising my anxiety levels.
我把车里的暖风打开了  结果喷出了呕吐物
I turned on the heat in my car and some vomit came out,
所以我的焦虑程度  高到这了
so my levels-- right up there.
同志们
Hey, guys.
介不介意艾米丽跟我们一起吃
Mind if Emily joins us for lunch?
-当然可以  -来吧  没问题
- Yeah, sure. - Yeah, no problem. Of course not.
我听说你们最近在玩一个小游戏
So I hear you guys have been playing a little game.
我们只是开玩笑而已
Well, um, we were just kidding around.
你们也许认为拉杰的贴心和敏感很好笑
Well, you may think it's funny that Raj is sweet and sensitive,
但我觉得那是性感
but I think it's sexy.
你嘴里怎么有狗毛
Ugh, why is there dog hair in your mouth?